

Panche Shterjovski

Digital Marketing

Professional

How to reach me:

Cell:

+389 70 395 687

Email:

shterjovski@gmail.com

Linkedin:

Public profile

Adress:

Ul. Dimo Hadzi Dimov 29, 1/4, Kisela Voda, Skopje, North Macedonia

Languages & Professional Skills

Mother tongue: Macedonian English: Spoken interaction: advanced; Writing: proficiency

Marketing Tools & Other:

HubSpot & Salesforce CRM, Retargeting/Remarketing, Google Ads, Docs, All social media platforms, AdRoll, WordPress, Adobe Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Camtasia, Automation

Personal Profile

I am a digital marketer with 8 yrs of experience in the areas of B2B & B2C marketing, as well ecommerce & retail.

Educational Training

American City University Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)

- 2006-2007
- International business & marketing
- Euro College Kumanovo (ACU Cheyenne, WY, USA program)

London City College

Advanced Diploma in Business Administration

- 2004-2006
- London City College LCC (London, UK)

Chartered Management Institute Certificate

- 2004
- London, UK

Career Summary

Senior Digital Coordinator <u>Cylindo Aps Denmark</u> Sept 2017 to present

- B2B Digital Marketing
- Product & Client Marketing, Lead generation
- CRM, SEM, SEO, PPC, Display, Social, ABM
- Web & graphic design, video creation

Product Marketing Specialist Seavus Feb 2017 - Aug 2017

- Product Marketing
- Web & graphic design, video creation
- Email marketing

Ecommerce Manager <u>Ekupi.eu</u> Croatia Feb 2013 - Jan 2017

- Product categories management
- Web & graphic design
- Social, PPC, Email Marketing

Commercial Specialist Cosmofon, ONE, ONE.vip Oct 2007 - Mar 2012

 Product marketing, trade marketing and the merchandising process